Guide to the John Melmoth Dow papers, 1798-1918.
Dow, John Melmoth papers, 1798-1918.
- Publications, 1854-1891
  - Extract from Proceedings of United States National Museum, 1886 (Box 12)
  - Directory of Scientific Societies of Washington, 1890-1892 (Box 12)
  - Extract from American Naturalist, 1891; Baur, G. (Box 12)
  - Extract from Art, 1854-09-20 (Box 12)
  - The Conchologists' Exchange, 1886 (Box 12)
    Vol. 1, No. 4
    Philadelphia
  - Revue Sur Le Systeme D'Inoculations Curatives Du Docteur Telephe Desmatis, 1862 (Box 12)
    Bordeaux
  - Note Sur Les Sepultures Indiennes Du Department de Chiriqu (Etat de Panama), 1865 (Box 12)
  - Une Epidemie de Variole A Bordeaux, 1870 (Box 12)
  - Otia Botanica Hamburgensia, 1878 (Box 12)
  - Proyecto de Arregio De La Deuda Interna & Esterna De La Republica, 1886 (Box 12)
  - Article from The Ibis, 1865; Sclater, Philip Lutley (Box 12)
    Describes a new species of Tanager of the Genus Iridornis
  - Synopsis Avium Tanagrinarum - A Descriptive Catalogue of the Known Species of Tanagers, 1856; Sclater, Philip Lutley (Box 12)
  - Article from Proceedings of the Zoological Society of London, 1868; Sclater, Philip Lutley (Box 12)
    Notes on the pelicans living in the Society's gardens
  - Monographic List of the Copeoptera of the Genus Plusiotis of America, North of Panama, with Descriptions of Several New Species, 1875; Boucard, Adolphe (Box 12)
  - Folia Orchidacea - An Enumeration of the Known Species of Orchids, 1859 (Box 12)
  - Exploration of the Ruins and Site of Copan, Central American, 1886; Maudsley, A. P. (Box 12)
  - The Charter, By-Laws, and Regulations of the Zoological Society of London, 1868 (Box 12)
  - A List of The Fellows and Honorary, Foreign, and Corresponding Members Medalists of the Zoological Society of London, 1877, 1881, 1884 (Box 12)
  - Guide to the Gardens of the Zoological Society of London, 1888; Sclater, Philip Lutley (Box 12)
  - Report of the Council of the Zoological Society for the Year 1891, 1892 (Box 12)
  - Additional material, photographs, Undated (Box 13)
- Mapcase Folders, 1861-1892
  - Business Records, 1861-1892 (Mapcase-folder 1)
    Contains reports, financial records, and charts
  - Presidential Election Bulletin, 1872-01-31 (Mapcase-folder 2)
    Boletin Oficial